Vibrant Media

Pro-Privacy. Cookie-Free. Always Contextual.

Privacy Policy
--------------

We take the privacy of your data seriously. This policy is designed to help you learn about Vibrant’s data practices. Please do read it carefully.

References to “Vibrant/we/us” means Vibrant Media Limited. The terms “you” and “your” means you as a user of our Website and our Network.

This Privacy Policy explains how we use information we collect via our own website www.vibrantmedia.com/en/ (Website) and on any of our client publishers’ websites, which are part of our advertising network (Network), for example, when you click on advertisements we have served on our clients’ websites.

Please read our Privacy Policy carefully to understand the views and practices of Vibrant regarding your personal information. This Privacy Policy (together with our Cookie Statement) sets out the basis on which any personal information Vibrant collects from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us.

If you have any questions or queries, please contact us using the details set out at the end of this policy.

We occasionally modify our Privacy Policy and will post those changes on this page so that you remain aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we disclose it. Please check our Privacy Policy frequently to ensure that you are aware of any changes.

Topics
------

1. [Collection and Use of Information on this Website](#1)
2. [Collection and Use of Information through Our Technology](#2)
3. [Who else may use your information](#3)
4. [Cookies and other technologies](#4)
5. [Security](#5)
6. [Participation in self-regulatory programs](#6)
7. [Information access](#7)
8. [Contact details for additional questions and/or to issue a complaint](#8 "Contact details for additional questions and/or to issue a complaint")

**1\. COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION ON THIS WEBSITE**
---------------------------------------------------------

1.1 Our Website is directed at our clients who we intend to do business with. It is not directed at consumers. We use this business contact information primarily in order to make our technology available to our customers and clients, contact customers and potential customers who have provided information to us about our technology, administer accounts, and respond to questions and issues you might have.

1.2 The following personal and identifiable information may be provided by you when you visit our Website:

1.2.1 when you register or complete our enquiry form, you may provide us your name, address, e-mail address and/or telephone number etc. This information allows us to contact you with the information/services you may request from us. We may also ask you to give us other optional contact information, for example your mobile phone number.

1.2.2 if you contact us via our Website, we may keep a record of that email, form or comment.

1.2.3 if you agree to provide a testimonial about your experience with us, we will collect your name and comments and may display them on our Website.

1.2.4 we may also ask you to complete surveys for research purposes from time to time.

1.3 Your personal and identifiable information may be used in the following ways:

1.3.1 to register you as a user of our Website;

1.3.2 to identify you when you visit our Website, including to assist with logging you in;

1.3.3 to provide service(s) and information to you as an actual or potential user of our technology and to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us;

1.3.4 to notify you about changes to services and/or our Website.

1.3.5 your IP address may be used to help diagnose problems with servers and to administer the Website;

1.3.6 to ensure that content from our Website is presented in the most effective manner;

1.3.7 to help administer our Website generally; and as otherwise described at the time of collection

1.4 In addition, under European privacy law, some information that is collected automatically through the Website is considered personal data. Such information includes information such as your IP host address, pages viewed, browser type, Internet browsing and usage habits, Internet Service Provider, domain name, the time/date of your visit to this Website, the referring URL and your computer’s operating system. This information is typically collected in log files on the Website’s servers. The purpose of this collection is as follows:

1.4.1 your IP address may be used to help diagnose problems with servers and to administer the Website;

1.4.2 to ensure that content from our Website is presented in the most effective manner;

1.4.3 to help administer our Website generally; and as otherwise described at the time of collection

1.5 By using our Website and submitting your information, you consent tothe collection and use of your information by us as described in this Privacy Policy;

1.6 Please note that our Website may, from time to time, contain links to and from other websites. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites and the information practices of those websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Please check the individual privacy policy of any website before you submit any personal data to them.

1.7 Cookies We use cookies on this Website. Cookies are small text files placed in a visitor’s browser. Cookies make using our Website easier for visitors by, among other things, saving their login preferences and improving the usability of our Website. Through your browser settings, you may disable certain cookies. For more information about cookies please visit the Vibrant Media Cookie Statement by clicking here. We may use cookies on this Website, as well as log file data, to manage the Website and improve its usability.

1.8 Updating / Deleting your Personal Data If you’d like us to update, correct, or delete any personal data that you have provided to us on this Website, please send your request to us by clicking here and we will process your request.

1.9 Where you have given us your contact details on a form on the Website or have emailed us in order to request additional information from us, we will rely on your consent to use your information for such purpose. You may revoke that consent at any time. Please see the How To Object and Opt Out section below for information as to how you may withdraw your consent. We use the information collected from you through this Website as necessary for our legitimate interests. These legitimate interests include our interests in providing, maintaining, operating and improving this Website and ultimately the services we provide to our customers and clients.

**2\. COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION THROUGH OUR TECHNOLOGY**
----------------------------------------------------------------

2.1 We place advertisements on websites operated by our client publishers (i.e. through our Network). Our products include Vibrant In-Text Ads, Vibrant In-Image Ads and Vibrant Display Ads. For more information about our products, [click here](http://54.162.255.12/en/contact-us/). Other than serving advertisements as referred to above, we do not modify, control or influence any content on our client publishers’ websites.

2.2 Our technology is designed primarily to facilitate the delivery of contextual advertising. For example, we may place advertisements triggered from highlighted keywords within the text of web content on a client publisher’s website so that when you move your mouse over a word or phrase of interest, a relevant advertisement will appear (for example, an advertisement for cars which appears when you move your mouse over the word ‘car’ while reading an automotive news article).

2.3 We may collect information about a visitor’s interactions with the advertising we place on the Network, which we may use to provide more relevant advertisements aligned with your current interests. This process is called “Interest Matching”, and examples of how we may carry out Interest Matching are set out below:

2.3.1 One example is that, if you interact with one of our advertisements (for example, by hovering your mouse over one of the keywords we have underscored), we may use information about your interaction using cookies and other technologies (please see our [Cookie Statement](http://54.162.255.12/en/cookie-policy/) for more details) and draw inferences from your visit in order to provide you with an advertisement that is more relevant, interesting, and useful for you.

2.3.2 As another example, we may use our technology to identify a visitor’s interests by gathering web viewing data (e.g. web pages visited, browser type, referring URL, Internet service provider, a computer’s or device’s operating system, and date and time of visits) using cookies and other technologies (please see our [Cookie Statement](http://54.162.255.12/en/cookie-policy/) for more details).

2.3.3 We may also engage in behavioural retargeting that allows us and some of our advertising partners to display advertising to you when you are on a website in our Network, based on your browsing patterns and interactions with a website (which may or may not be part of our Network). For example, if you have visited the website of an online retailer, you may see ads on websites in our Network from that same retailer displaying the products that you were viewing on the retailer’s website.

2.3.4 In the case of all the examples above, the information collected and used does not include such personally identifiable information as your name, street address, e-mail address or telephone number.

2.4 Aggregate and non-personally identifiable web viewing and computer data is also collected and used for other purposes including advertisement delivery and reporting, measuring the effectiveness of a campaign, optimizing a campaign, and for operational purposes. We may also combine web viewing data with information (e.g. demographic data) provided by other entities to help make our advertiser clients’ advertising more relevant.

2.5 If you’d like to opt-out from having Vibrant Media collect your information for Interest Matching advertising as described in section 2.3 of this Privacy Policy, please see our [Cookie Statement](http://54.162.255.12/en/cookie-policy/). When you opt out, we will place an opt-out cookie on your browser. The opt-out cookie tells us not to collect your information to tailor our online advertisement campaigns. However, we may continue to collect certain data for basic ad serving and other purposes such as counting the number of times a keyword has been clicked.

2.6 Our legal bases for collecting and using this personal data are as follows: (a) consent – we will not place cookies on your browser if you do not give us consent to do so. You will continue to receive advertising through our technology but such advertising will be only contextual which means that it is being placed where you can see it based only on the words or images on the page of the website you are viewing. (b) legitimate interests including our interests in providing, improving, and customizing our technology for our clients and customers and providing you with relevant advertising and content, unless those interests are overridden by your interests or fundamental rights requiring protection of personal information.

2.7 We process data primarily in the European Economic Area. However, we are a global company and occasionally will transfer data outside the EEA. In such instances, the data is pseudo-anonymised so that no data can be tied back to any user.

In addition, we use standard contractual clauses approved by the European Commission and may rely on the European Commission’s decisions about the adequacy of safeguards in certain countries, as applicable, including for data transfers from the EEA to the United States and other countries. You can contact us to request a copy of our Standard Contractual Clauses.

**3\. WHO ELSE MAY USE YOUR INFORMATION**
-----------------------------------------

3.1 We may share the information described in sections 1 and 2 of this Privacy Policy with third parties, or transfer such information to a third party, in the following circumstances:

3.1.1 to other members of our group, our partners and service providers (for example people who provide technical services to the Website) for the purpose of managing or administering certain aspects of our Website, or to help us develop new services;

3.1.2 to a third party or successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of all or substantially all of Vibrant’s assets, bankruptcy, or other corporate change.

3.1.3 if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with any legal obligation and/or in order to enforce or apply any other agreements between you and Vibrant; or

3.1.4 to protect the rights, property or safety of us or our users.

3.2 In addition to the information that we collect, a number of third parties may collect certain data when you visit websites using our technology. These third parties include:

3.2.1 our website publisher clients that operate websites that use our technology, who may use their own cookies and other technologies to collect information about the content of the sites that you visit and the advertising that appears on those sites; and

3.2.2 our advertiser clients that use our services to service advertising content, who may use cookies and other technologies within their advertising content to collect information about your use of the relevant websites and advertising

For more information on how third parties use cookies in our Network, please [click here to read our Cookie Statement.](http://54.162.255.12/en/cookie-policy/)

**4\. COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES**
--------------------------------------

4.1 ‘Cookies’ are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser’s settings to prevent that. We use cookies and other technologies on our Website and on the websites and advertisements in our Network.

4.2 We have created a Cookie Policy to explain how we use cookies and how you may manage our use of cookies and other tracking devices. [Please click here to read our Cookie Statement.](http://54.162.255.12/en/cookie-policy/)

**5\. SECURITY**
----------------

We have in place administrative, physical, and technical measures designed to protect the confidentiality and integrity of your data that we hold. These measures may include encryption and employment of information storage security technologies to restrict access to our network. In spite of these efforts, you should be aware that no method of transmitting information via the internet is completely secure.

**6\. PARTICIPATION IN SELF-REGULATORY PROGRAMS**
-------------------------------------------------

We support the cross industry, Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioural Advertising as managed by the European Digital Advertising Alliance (“EDAA”) (for more information [click here](https://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/)) as well as the EDAA’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Multi-Site Data, and, in particular, the use of the Ad Choices icon. In support of the EDAA and to provide consumers with enhanced transparency, we display the Ad Choices Icon advertisements delivered across our network to help consumers understand how their data is being used and provides choices for consumers who want more control. The Ad Choices icon is customarily displayed within the frame of our advertisement. The Ad Choices icon provides information (and links to other information) on online ads, who may be collecting and using online data, and how you can exercise choice with respect to those companies participating in the EDAA program. Vibrant Media also (1) is a member of the Internet Advertising Bureau and abides by IAB’s Member Code of Conduct which you can review by [clicking here](https://www.iab.net/public_policy/codeofconduct) and (2) is an NAI member and adheres to the NAI Code of Conduct (“NAI”) opt-out tool for behavioural advertising, which you can review at [https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices).

**7\. INFORMATION ACCESS**
--------------------------

7.1 Vibrant Media Limited is registered with the UK Information Commissioner’s office as a Data Controller in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 (DPA) with registration number Z526181X. The DPA provides a framework to ensure that personal information is collected and handled properly and gives individuals certain rights to know what information is held about them. More information can be found at [www.ico.gov.uk](http://www.ico.gov.uk/).

7.2 If you are located in the EEA, you have certain rights under European privacy law to access personal data held about you and you can do this by contacting us at the details set out at the end of this policy. You can also request us to correct any factual inaccuracies in information we hold or delete any of that information from our records. In many cases where we process your information, you may also have a right to restrict or limit the ways in which we use your information, and to object to the processing of your personal information. You also have a right to obtain a copy of your personal information in an easily accessible format. For these purposes, please contact us at privacy.team@54.162.255.12. However, although we make predictions about users’ interests based on the information through our technology as described in this Privacy Policy, we don’t know who you are. Accordingly, if we receive a request from you and we cannot identify you (even if you provide us with additional information), we may not be able to assist you in exercising these rights.

7.3 If you are located in the EEA and we can properly identify you, you have a number of rights with regard to your personal information. For example, you have the right to access your information and to have inaccuracies in your personal information corrected.

**8\. CONTACT DETAILS FOR ADDITIONAL QUESTIONS AND/OR TO ISSUE A COMPLAINT**
----------------------------------------------------------------------------

If you have any questions or comments, or complaints about our Website (www.vibrantmedia.com/en/) or about this privacy statement, please contact us by one of the methods below:

Via mail: Vibrant Media, Ltd. 33 Queen Street, London, EC4R 1BR  
Via email: [intellitxtsupport@54.162.255.12](mailto:intellitxtsupport@54.162.255.12)  
Via telephone: 020 740 0000

Get started with the leader of contextual marketing.
----------------------------------------------------

We partner with Advertisers and Agencies to deliver engaging brand experiences that are relevant to what people care about in the very moment.

* 
* 
* 
* 

All Vibrant Media ad experiences are downloaded to the user’s browser on-demand, guaranteeing that they always receive the most up-to-date ad creative software solutions.  
  
Copyright © 2024 Vibrant Media, All Rights Reserved.    

We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept All”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies. However, you may visit "Cookie Settings" to provide a controlled consent.

Cookie Settings Accept All

Manage consent

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. These cookies ensure basic functionalities and security features of the website, anonymously.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-analytics | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Analytics". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-functional | 11 months | The cookie is set by GDPR cookie consent to record the user consent for the cookies in the category "Functional". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessary | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookies is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Necessary". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-others | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Other. |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-performance | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Performance". |
| viewed\_cookie\_policy | 11 months | The cookie is set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin and is used to store whether or not user has consented to the use of cookies. It does not store any personal data. |

Functional

 functional

Functional cookies help to perform certain functionalities like sharing the content of the website on social media platforms, collect feedbacks, and other third-party features.

Performance

 performance

Performance cookies are used to understand and analyze the key performance indexes of the website which helps in delivering a better user experience for the visitors.

Analytics

 analytics

Analytical cookies are used to understand how visitors interact with the website. These cookies help provide information on metrics the number of visitors, bounce rate, traffic source, etc.

Advertisement

 advertisement

Advertisement cookies are used to provide visitors with relevant ads and marketing campaigns. These cookies track visitors across websites and collect information to provide customized ads.

Others

 others

Other uncategorized cookies are those that are being analyzed and have not been classified into a category as yet.

Save & Accept
